myamplifiers.com 2019-02-23

# Privacy Policy - MyAmplifiers | MyAmplifiers

### MyAmplifiers privacy policy

 **7H trading ltd**  
13/1 Line Wall Road,  
Gibraltar

This Privacy Policy was created with the aim of demonstration our firm commitment to your privacy when making orders with us. 

Please, read the Privacy Policy statements outlined below. Your using the website and placing orders with us automatically means your full agreement to all of the statements of the current Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this policy, please, do not access or use this website.

### Collection of information

We never collect any information without your permission. Your using this website and placing orders with us means that you allow collection of information by us. The information we collect is used for internal purposes and is *NEVER passed or sold to any third parties. We use and collect your data as stated below.

### Non-personally Identifiable Information

This kind of information cannot identify you as a personality. This information is statistical data, used for the purposes of the current website improving. It includes the information about your use of this website, i.e. the pages you browse through, the route you have followed to find a page interesting for you, referral websites that led you to our webpage, search phrases you used while searching for our website in Search Engines, your IP address, and other non-personal information. The gathered data is manually analyzed in order to make improvements in navigation and functioning. The information is used by our team only and never passed to any third parties.

### Personally Identifiable Information

This information can identify you personally. Personally identifiable information is provided by you on a voluntary basis. This data is provided for the purposes of registering with the website and for enabling us to process and fulfil your orders. The information includes your username, your name, email address, shipping address, billing address, your credit card, or other payment information. This data is collected while you set up an account, perform checkouts, send us your feedback, etc. This data is used for internal use only and is *never passed to any third parties.

### PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USAGE

When ordering a product or just registering at MyAmplifiers, you may need to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.

The information about you can be collected when you register on the website, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, download specifications, fill out a form or contact our managers in the live chat on our site. The collected information can be used in the following ways:

  * To make our user's experience personalized so that we could offer you products in which you are more likely to be interested.
  * To let us offer you a more targeted customer service responding to your requests.
  * To manage a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To process your order and your transaction quicklier.
  * To send you notifications regarding your order or promotional emails concerning our products and services.
  * To follow up with you after communication in live chat, via email or call back requests

  **We collect information about you from various sources:**

 **Information that is provided by you**

Generally, you don’t need to provide any personal details in order to navigate on our website. However, in some cases a registration can be required and, by doing so, you will need to provide us with certain information. For example, if you need to get in touch with our managers, you will be asked to provide your email address, user name (which may be a pseudonym as well as your real name) and your phone number (optionally). In addition, if you purchase a product, you will also need to provide your real name, billing and shipping address.Note, please, that if you have shopped with us using a credit or debit card, we always securely collect and store this payment card information.

 **Information that is collected automatically**

Some types of information is collected automatically as the result of using of the website, or through the use of web analytics services as described in our Cookies Policy. This information may include the following:

  * the site that you visited prior to visiting MyAmplifiers;
  * specific actions that you take while navigating on the site, including the pages that you visit;
  * the time, frequency and duration of your visits;
  * your location data (e.g. GPS);
  * cookies data and similar technology in accordance with our Cookies Policy

### VISITOR'S INFORMATION PROTECTION

Our website is regularly scanned for the purpose of detecting possible security holes as well as vulnerabilities in order to ensure that your visit of our website is safe. Moreover, the information containing your personal details is stored behind secured networks and can be accessed by a limited number of persons having special rights to such systems and are obliged to keep the information confidential.

A variety of security measures is implemented to guarantee the safety of your personal information while placing orders, submits, or accessing your personal data. A special gateway provider is used to process all transactions which means that any of you billing details are not stored in our database.

### CAN SPAM ACT

The CAN-SPAM Act is a regulation setting the rules and establishing requirements for any types of commercial information: commercial emails, commercial messages, etc, thus, letting stop its recipients from the reception of these ones, and spelling out tough penalties for violations.

Your email address can be used for the following purposes:

  * Send information, answer to different kinds of requests or questions.
  * Process order information and send notifications and updates regarding the orders
  * Send you information related to the product and/or service you are interested in.
  * Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred

In order to be in conformity with CANSPAM requirements we respect the following principles:

  * Not using false neither misleading subjects or email addresses
  * Identifying the message as an advertisement in a reasonable way
  * Indicating the physical address or site headquarters of our business
  * Treating opt-out/unsubscribe requests ASAP
  * Letting users unsubscribe following the link contained in each email

If you want us to unsubscribe you from receiving our future emails, please, follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and you will be quickly removed from MyAmplifiers email list.

### Disclaimer

[Myamplifiers.com](https://www.myamplifiers.com/) does not make any express or implied warranties, representations or endorsements whatsoever (including, without limitation, the implied warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose) with regard to the web site, the materials, any products, information or service provided through the web site, or any sites listed therein, and the web site will not be liable for any cost or damage arising either directly or indirectly from any such transaction. The web site does not warrant that it will be uninterrupted or error-free or that defects in it will be corrected. The web site is provided on an "as is, as available" basis.

### *Disclosure

We reserve the right to disclose any information in case we are necessitated to do that in the course of legal proceedings by a legal act. The right to disclose you personally identifiable information is also reserved by us if we are fully convinced that the information must be disclosed to protect our rights and/or to obey any valid legal act.

### Delivery Condition

In case we have any doubts regarding shipping address we send you the email of address verification and proceed your order only after updated shipping instructions received. All items get delivered from the manufacture in Hong Kong directly.

Unfortunately, we can't control all the cases at customs, so if you have any problems, please, contact us immediately before paying any custom fees. If you didn't contact us and payed fees, we are not responsible for this explicit costs.

 _Please, note that due to strictness of local Customs delivery to such countries as Saudi Arabia, Cyprus and Egypt may take up to 3-4 weeks._
